onewayshopping.com 2013-07-28

# Onewayshopping.com – Privacy Policy

Updated 4/3/2011

**About this privacy statement**

This Privacy Policy outlines some of the types of personal information we receive and collect, and how we use that information. We hope this Privacy Policy will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal information with us.

**Application of this Privacy Statement**

At Onewayshopping.com ("Onewayshopping") we want you to know exactly how and when we collect and use information that can specifically identify you, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address ("personal information"). We do not require that you provide, nor do we collect, any personal information if you are just browsing the Site. We may offer on the Site non-transactional and transaction based services ("Service(s)") in which, subject to applicable terms and availability, you may participate (e.g., submitting product reviews or becoming a Member to buy. In order to provide you with the Services you request, Onewayshopping may require that you first provide certain personal information, which we determine is reasonably necessary in order for us to fulfill your request. If you indicate an interest in participating in a Service, we will identify what specific personal information you must provide prior to collecting such information. Any personal information which we collect from you will only be used for the purposes identified in this Privacy Statement, the Onewayshopping Terms of Use and your applicable Member Agreement with Onewayshopping, and as may otherwise be indicated at the time the information is collected.

**Information collected**

We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that does not identify you. The information that we collect is considered necessary for performing a preliminary evaluation of your qualifications to receive applicable products and/or services.

**Cookies and web beacons**

When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website.

**Log files**

Like most standard website servers we use log files. Log files store information including browser type, internet protocol (IP) addresses, internet service provider (ISP), date/time stamp referring/exit pages, platform type, and number of clicks, and are used to analyze trends, administer the Websites, track users' movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We use your IP address at times to help identify you as you browse and to gather broad technical and demographic information on who uses our Websites. We do not tie log files to personally identifiable information.

**How We Use Your Information**

**General:** In general we may use information we collect about you to:

  * Supply the products and services that you have requested; 
  * Manage your account and provide you with customer support; 
  * Communicate with you via email, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us or third parties;
  * Allows other users of our service to learn about you and your interests through information you make available on your profile;
  * Verify your eligibility to receive products and/or services
  * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services, or content, or products, services or content offered by others;
  * Communicate with you by e-mail, postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to you either from us, our sister IAC companies or other third parties;
  * Develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site and other sites

**With whom we share your information**

We want you to understand when and with whom we may share personal or other information we have collected about you or your activities on our web site or while using our services.

**Personal information.** We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. We may share personal information with:

  * Authorized service providers: We may share your personal information with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality and connectivity, and supporting any contests, sweepstakes, surveys and/or other features that may be offered through our website. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.
  * Business partners: When you make engage in promotions offered through our website or our services, we may share personal information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant's offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.

**Contact us**

If you have any questions about this Website Privacy Statement, the practices of the Websites, or your use of the Websites, please contact us at:

[privacy@onewayshopping.com](mailto:privacy@onewayshopping.com) or MAIL:  
One Way Shopping - LEGAL   
7065 Westpointe blvd, suite 308,  
Orlando FL 32835

**Opting out**

We understand you may not want to receive promotional email from us or from our partners and advertisers. You can choose to opt out of receiving promotional email communications from us by selecting to opt out if and when you register on our Websites, by following the unsubscribe instructions in the email communication you receive from us, or by contacting us directly. You can stop us from sharing your contact information with our partners and advertisers for direct marketing purposes either by selecting to opt out if and when you register on our Websites, by following the unsubscribe instructions in the email communication you receive, or by contacting the partner or advertiser directly.

**Links to Other Sites**

The Onewayshopping Service contains links to other websites. Onewayshopping.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these sites. If you have concerns about how other websites collect and use information about you, make sure to read that site's own privacy policy.

**Security**

Onewayshopping.com uses physical, electronic and administrative safeguards, including advanced firewall and password protection for our databases, designed to protect the security of information. We restrict access to your personal information to employees that need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Other Information**

**a. Child Use.**  
We do not knowingly collect personal information from, or sell products for purchase by, persons under the age of 18. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. Do not provide information to us, or purchase from this Site, if you are under the age of 18.

**b. Legal Disclaimer.**  
We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our Site. 

**c. Notification of Changes.**  
Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Policy will change accordingly. You should check our Site frequently to recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If we decide to change our email practices, we will post those changes to the Site so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
